<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ivanka Trump Archives - WWV Nacion</title>
	<atom:link href="//wwv.nacion.com/tag/ivanka-trump/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>//wwv.nacion.com/tag/ivanka-trump/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:54:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Ivanka Trump takes the stand in former President Donald Trump&#8217;s civil fraud trial</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ivanka Trump, daughter of former President Donald Trump, has been called to the witness stand...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/">Ivanka Trump takes the stand in former President Donald Trump&#8217;s civil fraud trial</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ivanka Trump, daughter of former President Donald Trump, has been called to the witness stand Wednesday to answer questions regarding fraudulent financial documents filed by the Trump Organization.</p>
<p>Ivanka Trump, who is not a defendant, is expected to be the last witness called by the state attorney general&#8217;s legal team in a civil fraud trial that will determine the penalties faced by other members of the Trump family.</p>
<p>She had been the executive vice president of development and acquisitions at the Trump Organization. During questioning led by AG lawyer Louis Solomon, Trump was asked about her knowledge of her father&#8217;s statements of financial conditions.</p>
<p>Trump was asked about her involvement in executing the purchase of the Trump National Doral property in Miami, Fla. The attorney general&#8217;s lawsuit alleges that Donald Trump&#8217;s inflated statements were used to secure a $125 million loan from Deutsche Bank and were regularly submitted to the bank to fulfill Donald Trump&#8217;s financial reporting requirements as guarantor on the loan.</p>
<p>Ivanka Trump, former President Donald Trump&#8217;s daughter, enters New York State Supreme Court for his civil fraud trial on Wednesday in New York City.<br />
Spencer Platt/Getty Images<br />
Ivanka Trump testified that she didn&#8217;t recall if the bank asked for the statements or if she offered them.</p>
<p>A judge says Trump is liable for fraud in New York civil lawsuit<br />
LAW<br />
A judge says Trump is liable for fraud in New York civil lawsuit<br />
The former president has been accused by state Attorney General Letitia James of being a part of a scheme that involved inflating or deflating the value of assets in order to secure better business, insurance and banking deals between 2011 and 2021. Trump&#8217;s two older sons, Donald Jr. and Eric, are also defendants in the lawsuit. Judge Arthur Engoron has already ruled that Trump is liable of fraud.</p>
<p>Jesus Suarez, one of the attorneys in the Trump legal team, conducted a cross-examination of Ivanka Trump, making her the only Trump family member who received questioning from the defense.</p>
<p>Suarez asked her if she was personally responsible for submitting, preparing, reviewing or approving the financial statements. To all, Trump answered no.</p>
<p>Several months ago, Ivanka Trump&#8217;s attorney successfully argued that any related actions Ivanka had at the Trump Organization happened before the statute of limitations kicked in.</p>
<p>Outside the courtroom, James argued that Ivanka Trump personally benefited from the inflated financial statements, even as she stepped away from the Trump Organization.</p>
<p>Donald Trump&#8217;s legal team will begin their defense next week, with the goal of being done by mid-December.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/">Ivanka Trump takes the stand in former President Donald Trump&#8217;s civil fraud trial</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
