<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Virginia Democrats Archives - WWV Nacion</title>
	<atom:link href="//wwv.nacion.com/tag/virginia-democrats/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>//wwv.nacion.com/tag/virginia-democrats/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Virginia Democrats sweep legislative elections after campaigning on abortion rights</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virginia Democrats]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=33</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Democrats who campaigned on protecting abortion rights swept Tuesday’s legislative elections, retaking full control...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/">Virginia Democrats sweep legislative elections after campaigning on abortion rights</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Democrats who campaigned on protecting abortion rights swept Tuesday’s legislative elections, retaking full control of the General Assembly after two years of divided power.</p>
<p>The outcome is a sharp loss for Gov. Glenn Youngkin and his fellow Republicans, who exerted a great deal of energy, money and political capital on their effort to secure a GOP trifecta.</p>
<p>“It’s official: there will be absolutely no abortion ban legislation sent to Glenn Youngkin’s desk for the duration of his term in office, period, as we have thwarted MAGA Republicans’ attempt to take total control of our government and our bodies,” Virginia Senate Democratic Caucus Chair Mamie Locke said in a statement referencing Donald Trump’s “Make America Great Again” slogan.</p>
<p>Virginia was one of just four states holding legislative races this year, and it’s something of a microcosm of other closely divided states that will be critical in next year’s presidential election. That fueled outsized interest in the expensive, hard-fought legislative races, as both parties closely monitored the results for signs about voter moods heading into the 2024 campaign.</p>
<p>With a full statehouse majority, Democrats will have even greater leeway to thwart Youngkin’s policy agenda, though they will have to work with him to advance their own.</p>
<p>Every General Assembly seat was on the ballot this year, with the most competitive seats based in Hampton Roads and the suburbs of Richmond and Washington. Democrats flipped the House of Delegates and held the majority they’ve had in the Senate since 2020.</p>
<p>Candidates made their case to voters this cycle on the economy, the environment, public safety and schools, but no issue was more hotly contested than abortion in the last state in the South without new restrictions since the end of Roe v. Wade.</p>
<p>The results in Virginia — along with a win for abortion rights supporters on an Ohio ballot measure and Democratic Gov. Andy Beshear’s reelection in Kentucky — will comfort the national party as President Joe Biden and other Democrats are expected to prioritize abortion rights in next year’s campaign to energize their voters.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/">Virginia Democrats sweep legislative elections after campaigning on abortion rights</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
