<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives - WWV Nacion</title>
	<atom:link href="//wwv.nacion.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>//wwv.nacion.com/category/news/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Costa Rica inflation moderates fall in September</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Costa Rica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=36</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Costa Rica: Consumer prices falls at softer pace on an annual basis in September Consumer...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/">Costa Rica inflation moderates fall in September</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Costa Rica: Consumer prices falls at softer pace on an annual basis in September<br />
Consumer prices fell 2.2% year on year in September, a smaller drop than August’s 3.3% decrease. Looking at the details of the release, prices for food and non-alcoholic beverages plunged in September. Moreover, housing price growth softened. That said, prices for transportation declined at a more moderate rate.</p>
<p>The trend pointed down, with annual average inflation coming in at 2.9% in September (August: 4.0%).</p>
<p>Lastly, consumer prices rose 0.11% over the previous month in September, contrasting the 0.16% drop recorded in August. September’s figure was the highest reading since January.</p>
<p>Costa Rica: Staff Concluding Statement of the 2023 Article IV Mission, Fifth Review under the Extended Fund Facility, and Second Review Under the Resilience and Sustainability Facility Arrangement</p>
<p>San José: An International Monetary Fund (IMF) staff team, led by Mr. Ding Ding, visited San Jos é during October 18–27. The staff team held discussions on the 2023 Article IV consultation with the Costa Rican authorities. The consultation focused on how to institutionalize the significant progress achieved in the past few years over the medium term. The Costa Rican authorities and IMF staff also reached a staff-level agreement on the policies needed to complete the fifth review of the Extended Fund Facility (EFF) and the second assessment of reform measures under the Resilience and Sustainability Facility (RSF) Arrangement.</p>
<p>Despite strong growth momentum, inflation has declined sharply. Real GDP growth is expected to reach around 5 percent this year, supported by buoyant exports and recovering domestic demand. Growth is expected to moderate to 3½ percent in 2024, which is broadly in line with the medium-term potential growth rate. Headline inflation has been negative over the past four months as global commodity prices fell and a stronger currency helped to reduce goods prices. Inflation is expected to rise back within the Central Bank of Costa Rica (BCCR)’s tolerance band by mid-2024. The value of the colón has stabilized near its long run historical average in real effective terms and international reserves buffers are strong.</p>
<p>The rapid decline in inflation should allow monetary policy to return to a neutral setting by mid-2024, assuming the economy evolves according to staff’s baseline forecast. The BCCR appropriately raised interest rates (to 9 percent) in 2022 to counter the global inflation shock and anchor inflation expectations. As inflation receded, the BCCR appropriately lowered the policy rate and should continue to normalize its policy stance to ensure that inflation converges decisively to the BCCR’s target. Risks to inflation are broadly balanced as those from weak domestic price pressures are offset by the potential for higher global energy or other import prices. Policy decisions should continue to be data-dependent, forward-looking, and supported by clear and transparent communications, with due attention to the two-sided risks to inflation. Going forward, the authorities should persist in their efforts to further strengthen the BCCR’s autonomy, governance, and operational framework.</p>
<p>A deeper and more liquid foreign exchange (FX) market and greater exchange rate flexibility would strengthen the transmission of monetary policy to activity and inflation. Costa Rica has a shallow FX market and faces some degree of currency mismatch arising from dollarization. In principle, this could justify deploying targeted FX intervention to mitigate excessive exchange rate fluctuations. However, in most circumstances, the exchange rate should be allowed to move freely in response to market conditions. The BCCR should explore the reduction of the impact of its operations in the FX market by aligning the timing of BCCR purchases of FX on behalf of the non-financial public sector (NFPS) with the sale of FX to these entities. A more flexible exchange rate and greater transparency in BCCR FX operations would both allow monetary policy to have its full effect on activity and inflation and incentivize the deepening of the FX market (including the use of FX hedging instruments). To complement this more restrained approach to FX intervention, further institutional and technical reforms would be useful to improve the functioning of the FX market and strengthen market participants’ ability to manage currency risks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/">Costa Rica inflation moderates fall in September</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virginia Democrats sweep legislative elections after campaigning on abortion rights</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virginia Democrats]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=33</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Democrats who campaigned on protecting abortion rights swept Tuesday’s legislative elections, retaking full control...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/">Virginia Democrats sweep legislative elections after campaigning on abortion rights</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Democrats who campaigned on protecting abortion rights swept Tuesday’s legislative elections, retaking full control of the General Assembly after two years of divided power.</p>
<p>The outcome is a sharp loss for Gov. Glenn Youngkin and his fellow Republicans, who exerted a great deal of energy, money and political capital on their effort to secure a GOP trifecta.</p>
<p>“It’s official: there will be absolutely no abortion ban legislation sent to Glenn Youngkin’s desk for the duration of his term in office, period, as we have thwarted MAGA Republicans’ attempt to take total control of our government and our bodies,” Virginia Senate Democratic Caucus Chair Mamie Locke said in a statement referencing Donald Trump’s “Make America Great Again” slogan.</p>
<p>Virginia was one of just four states holding legislative races this year, and it’s something of a microcosm of other closely divided states that will be critical in next year’s presidential election. That fueled outsized interest in the expensive, hard-fought legislative races, as both parties closely monitored the results for signs about voter moods heading into the 2024 campaign.</p>
<p>With a full statehouse majority, Democrats will have even greater leeway to thwart Youngkin’s policy agenda, though they will have to work with him to advance their own.</p>
<p>Every General Assembly seat was on the ballot this year, with the most competitive seats based in Hampton Roads and the suburbs of Richmond and Washington. Democrats flipped the House of Delegates and held the majority they’ve had in the Senate since 2020.</p>
<p>Candidates made their case to voters this cycle on the economy, the environment, public safety and schools, but no issue was more hotly contested than abortion in the last state in the South without new restrictions since the end of Roe v. Wade.</p>
<p>The results in Virginia — along with a win for abortion rights supporters on an Ohio ballot measure and Democratic Gov. Andy Beshear’s reelection in Kentucky — will comfort the national party as President Joe Biden and other Democrats are expected to prioritize abortion rights in next year’s campaign to energize their voters.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/">Virginia Democrats sweep legislative elections after campaigning on abortion rights</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/virginia-democrats-sweep-legislative-elections-after-campaigning-on-abortion-rights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Kim Looking for Her Own Football Guy?</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/is-kim-looking-for-her-own-football-guy/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/is-kim-looking-for-her-own-football-guy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Is Kim]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=30</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are deep in the throes of football season, by which I mean that Taylor...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/is-kim-looking-for-her-own-football-guy/">Is Kim Looking for Her Own Football Guy?</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are deep in the throes of football season, by which I mean that Taylor Swift has been publicly dating an NFL guy for one month. And now, it seems another woman whose dating life is frequently the subject of wild speculation is wading into the end zone as well: Kim Kardashian. Pete Davidson’s most famous ex is rumored to be hanging out with one Odell Beckham Jr., wide receiver for the Baltimore Ravens.</p>
<p>Kim and OBJ were first linked — in gossip, at least — in September, when several outlets claimed they had been “hanging out casually,” though only in groups with mutual friends. (Beckham and his ex-girlfriend Lauren Wood, who share a son, broke up at some point earlier this year.) On Monday, Kim set off another flurry of rumors after she showed face at Beckham’s 31st birthday party in New York.</p>
<p>Still, no one seems to suspect these frequent hangouts are anything but friendly. E! News claimed in September that Kim is “not seriously dating anyone at the moment” and that she and OBJ simply have “a lot of mutual friends in common.” Her presence at OBJ’s birthday party is not exactly indicative of anything particularly flirty, either — they have indeed been running in the same social circle for years, and she was at his 30th birthday last year, too. Also, one source told “Page Six” that they spent the whole night chatting with the CEO of a sports-merch company. Doesn’t exactly sound like a date to me, but then again, neither does ice cream at Rite Aid. Perhaps a field-side appearance at the M&amp;T Bank Stadium lies somewhere in our future?</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/is-kim-looking-for-her-own-football-guy/">Is Kim Looking for Her Own Football Guy?</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/is-kim-looking-for-her-own-football-guy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Navy sees improved upkeep as hedge against strategic submarine dip</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/us-navy-sees-improved-upkeep-as-hedge-against-strategic-submarine-dip/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/us-navy-sees-improved-upkeep-as-hedge-against-strategic-submarine-dip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Navy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=27</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s counterintuitive,” the head of U.S. submarine forces acknowledges, but the Navy’s ballistic missile submarine...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/us-navy-sees-improved-upkeep-as-hedge-against-strategic-submarine-dip/">US Navy sees improved upkeep as hedge against strategic submarine dip</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s counterintuitive,” the head of U.S. submarine forces acknowledges, but the Navy’s ballistic missile submarine force is spending more time operating at sea while also seeing better material readiness rates.</p>
<p>The trend is encouraging, submarine leaders say, because an upcoming dip in the size of the fleet will mean these SSBNs will have to stay at sea longer and spend less time in maintenance, or risk not meeting national nuclear deterrence requirements.</p>
<p>U.S. Strategic Command requires that 10 SSBNs be available at any given time. The fleet has 14 boats today but will soon drop to just 10 and then only bounce back up to 12 as the current Ohio-class SSBNs reach the end of their planned service life and the new Columbia-class boats come online.</p>
<p>When the fleet stabilizes at 12 boats, it will only be able to afford having two vessels in maintenance at any given time, compared to the four that are often offline for maintenance today.</p>
<p>Vice Adm. William Houston, the commander of naval submarine forces, is conducting something of a dry run now — and he said it’s going well, with the fleet at “a higher [operating tempo] than we have historically been … while actually improving material readiness across the force.”</p>
<p>Houston told Defense News at the Naval Submarine League annual symposium here that he started the effort by basically forcing more ships to go to sea: he only allowed two to be in port, enabling 2,000 workers to focus on just two maintenance availabilities instead of spreading themselves thin trying to manage four.</p>
<p>What he found was that the teams performed better maintenance, and faster, when they were allowed to focus their efforts on fewer boats. As a result, the boats coming out of maintenance were in better material condition than they had been in the past.</p>
<p>This is in contrast to past Navy examples of increasing the operating tempo of certain platforms ­— amphibious ships and aircraft carriers in particular — to keep up with combatant commander requirements, but then seeing the material condition of these ships plummet when the repair yards couldn’t keep up with the subsequent increase in maintenance demands.</p>
<p>The Navy is in a precarious position with its SSBN fleet. Even in the best-case scenario where the new Columbia-class boats meet their construction and testing schedules and can go on their maiden deployments on time, the Navy will still find itself with just 10 boats in the inventory and having to keep them all operationally available all the time.</p>
<p>Rear Adm. Scott Pappano, the Program Executive Officer for Strategic Submarines, said this prospect makes the Navy uncomfortable, and so the service is considering putting up to five Ohio-class SSBNs into an 18-month maintenance availability that give them three more years of service life. The first of these life extensions could take place in fiscal 2029 with submarine Alaska, helping create a little extra margin during the Ohio-to-Columbia transition years.</p>
<p>Though the Navy is carefully monitoring the Ohio class to ensure the boats’ remaining service life isn’t consumed too quickly, Pappano told Defense News at the symposium that this situation is a wash: Houston is using the boats more, but he’s keeping them in better material condition.</p>
<p>Pappano said his office would continue to track this over the coming years to make sure the higher operational tempo today wouldn’t hurt the boats’ ability to make it to the end of their planned life, but he said he sees no reason now to be concerned.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/us-navy-sees-improved-upkeep-as-hedge-against-strategic-submarine-dip/">US Navy sees improved upkeep as hedge against strategic submarine dip</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/us-navy-sees-improved-upkeep-as-hedge-against-strategic-submarine-dip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ivanka Trump takes the stand in former President Donald Trump&#8217;s civil fraud trial</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ivanka Trump, daughter of former President Donald Trump, has been called to the witness stand...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/">Ivanka Trump takes the stand in former President Donald Trump&#8217;s civil fraud trial</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ivanka Trump, daughter of former President Donald Trump, has been called to the witness stand Wednesday to answer questions regarding fraudulent financial documents filed by the Trump Organization.</p>
<p>Ivanka Trump, who is not a defendant, is expected to be the last witness called by the state attorney general&#8217;s legal team in a civil fraud trial that will determine the penalties faced by other members of the Trump family.</p>
<p>She had been the executive vice president of development and acquisitions at the Trump Organization. During questioning led by AG lawyer Louis Solomon, Trump was asked about her knowledge of her father&#8217;s statements of financial conditions.</p>
<p>Trump was asked about her involvement in executing the purchase of the Trump National Doral property in Miami, Fla. The attorney general&#8217;s lawsuit alleges that Donald Trump&#8217;s inflated statements were used to secure a $125 million loan from Deutsche Bank and were regularly submitted to the bank to fulfill Donald Trump&#8217;s financial reporting requirements as guarantor on the loan.</p>
<p>Ivanka Trump, former President Donald Trump&#8217;s daughter, enters New York State Supreme Court for his civil fraud trial on Wednesday in New York City.<br />
Spencer Platt/Getty Images<br />
Ivanka Trump testified that she didn&#8217;t recall if the bank asked for the statements or if she offered them.</p>
<p>A judge says Trump is liable for fraud in New York civil lawsuit<br />
LAW<br />
A judge says Trump is liable for fraud in New York civil lawsuit<br />
The former president has been accused by state Attorney General Letitia James of being a part of a scheme that involved inflating or deflating the value of assets in order to secure better business, insurance and banking deals between 2011 and 2021. Trump&#8217;s two older sons, Donald Jr. and Eric, are also defendants in the lawsuit. Judge Arthur Engoron has already ruled that Trump is liable of fraud.</p>
<p>Jesus Suarez, one of the attorneys in the Trump legal team, conducted a cross-examination of Ivanka Trump, making her the only Trump family member who received questioning from the defense.</p>
<p>Suarez asked her if she was personally responsible for submitting, preparing, reviewing or approving the financial statements. To all, Trump answered no.</p>
<p>Several months ago, Ivanka Trump&#8217;s attorney successfully argued that any related actions Ivanka had at the Trump Organization happened before the statute of limitations kicked in.</p>
<p>Outside the courtroom, James argued that Ivanka Trump personally benefited from the inflated financial statements, even as she stepped away from the Trump Organization.</p>
<p>Donald Trump&#8217;s legal team will begin their defense next week, with the goal of being done by mid-December.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/">Ivanka Trump takes the stand in former President Donald Trump&#8217;s civil fraud trial</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/ivanka-trump-takes-the-stand-in-former-president-donald-trumps-civil-fraud-trial/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glenn Youngkin handed presidential buzzkill</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/glenn-youngkin-handed-presidential-buzzkill/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/glenn-youngkin-handed-presidential-buzzkill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glenn Youngkin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin didn&#8217;t get what he wanted, after Democrats seized total control of...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/glenn-youngkin-handed-presidential-buzzkill/">Glenn Youngkin handed presidential buzzkill</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin didn&#8217;t get what he wanted, after Democrats seized total control of the legislature on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Why it matters: Youngkin&#8217;s flirtation with taking on former President Trump in the 2024 election — and the media&#8217;s obsession — is finally coming to an end.</p>
<p>What I&#8217;m hearing: Those around him believe Youngkin&#8217;s too smart to enter the 2024 race — even if Republicans had triumphed last night and flipped the Senate.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t know anyone who knows him that thinks he&#8217;s going to run for president in 2024,&#8221; a person close to the Youngkin operation told me on Monday, asking to remain anonymous to speak candidly. Deadlines for several early states have passed, and more are about to, even if Youngkin publicly hasn&#8217;t ruled it out.<br />
Youngkin&#8217;s wife, Suzanne, has privately not wanted him to get into the race, according to two sources with knowledge of her thinking. She has worried for months, in particular, about putting her family in Trump&#8217;s crosshairs, one person said.<br />
Yes, but: Those in the governor&#8217;s orbit expect a Youngkin 2028 campaign. (In our current political age, one might say the 56-year-old isn&#8217;t yet old enough to be president.)</p>
<p>Youngkin&#8217;s office declined to comment.<br />
State of play: Since Youngkin can&#8217;t run for re-election under Virginia rules, he would leave the governor&#8217;s mansion in January 2026 with a generous runway for a White House bid.</p>
<p>In the meantime, there&#8217;s a Bloombergian playbook available to Youngkin.</p>
<p>Not the ill-fated Bloomberg 2020 campaign, but the example the former New York mayor set over the preceding decade when he went national to raise money for gun control.<br />
Youngkin could do the same on conservative causes, like selling his early voting model to skeptical Republicans.<br />
Between the lines: Perhaps one reason the former private equity exec played so long with the idea of a presidential bid: money. And the boost to his less-Trumpy, dad-vest brand.</p>
<p>Youngkin&#8217;s Spirit of Virginia PAC has raised $30 million since 2021, according to Open Secrets.<br />
Leveraging billionaire buzz — and fatcats like Rupert Murdoch urging him to run — meant 90% of the money came from large donors giving more than $10,000.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/glenn-youngkin-handed-presidential-buzzkill/">Glenn Youngkin handed presidential buzzkill</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/glenn-youngkin-handed-presidential-buzzkill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
