<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Costa Rica Archives - WWV Nacion</title>
	<atom:link href="//wwv.nacion.com/tag/costa-rica/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>//wwv.nacion.com/tag/costa-rica/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Costa Rica inflation moderates fall in September</title>
		<link>//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/</link>
					<comments>//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wwv]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Costa Rica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//wwv.nacion.com/?p=36</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Costa Rica: Consumer prices falls at softer pace on an annual basis in September Consumer...</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/">Costa Rica inflation moderates fall in September</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Costa Rica: Consumer prices falls at softer pace on an annual basis in September<br />
Consumer prices fell 2.2% year on year in September, a smaller drop than August’s 3.3% decrease. Looking at the details of the release, prices for food and non-alcoholic beverages plunged in September. Moreover, housing price growth softened. That said, prices for transportation declined at a more moderate rate.</p>
<p>The trend pointed down, with annual average inflation coming in at 2.9% in September (August: 4.0%).</p>
<p>Lastly, consumer prices rose 0.11% over the previous month in September, contrasting the 0.16% drop recorded in August. September’s figure was the highest reading since January.</p>
<p>Costa Rica: Staff Concluding Statement of the 2023 Article IV Mission, Fifth Review under the Extended Fund Facility, and Second Review Under the Resilience and Sustainability Facility Arrangement</p>
<p>San José: An International Monetary Fund (IMF) staff team, led by Mr. Ding Ding, visited San Jos é during October 18–27. The staff team held discussions on the 2023 Article IV consultation with the Costa Rican authorities. The consultation focused on how to institutionalize the significant progress achieved in the past few years over the medium term. The Costa Rican authorities and IMF staff also reached a staff-level agreement on the policies needed to complete the fifth review of the Extended Fund Facility (EFF) and the second assessment of reform measures under the Resilience and Sustainability Facility (RSF) Arrangement.</p>
<p>Despite strong growth momentum, inflation has declined sharply. Real GDP growth is expected to reach around 5 percent this year, supported by buoyant exports and recovering domestic demand. Growth is expected to moderate to 3½ percent in 2024, which is broadly in line with the medium-term potential growth rate. Headline inflation has been negative over the past four months as global commodity prices fell and a stronger currency helped to reduce goods prices. Inflation is expected to rise back within the Central Bank of Costa Rica (BCCR)’s tolerance band by mid-2024. The value of the colón has stabilized near its long run historical average in real effective terms and international reserves buffers are strong.</p>
<p>The rapid decline in inflation should allow monetary policy to return to a neutral setting by mid-2024, assuming the economy evolves according to staff’s baseline forecast. The BCCR appropriately raised interest rates (to 9 percent) in 2022 to counter the global inflation shock and anchor inflation expectations. As inflation receded, the BCCR appropriately lowered the policy rate and should continue to normalize its policy stance to ensure that inflation converges decisively to the BCCR’s target. Risks to inflation are broadly balanced as those from weak domestic price pressures are offset by the potential for higher global energy or other import prices. Policy decisions should continue to be data-dependent, forward-looking, and supported by clear and transparent communications, with due attention to the two-sided risks to inflation. Going forward, the authorities should persist in their efforts to further strengthen the BCCR’s autonomy, governance, and operational framework.</p>
<p>A deeper and more liquid foreign exchange (FX) market and greater exchange rate flexibility would strengthen the transmission of monetary policy to activity and inflation. Costa Rica has a shallow FX market and faces some degree of currency mismatch arising from dollarization. In principle, this could justify deploying targeted FX intervention to mitigate excessive exchange rate fluctuations. However, in most circumstances, the exchange rate should be allowed to move freely in response to market conditions. The BCCR should explore the reduction of the impact of its operations in the FX market by aligning the timing of BCCR purchases of FX on behalf of the non-financial public sector (NFPS) with the sale of FX to these entities. A more flexible exchange rate and greater transparency in BCCR FX operations would both allow monetary policy to have its full effect on activity and inflation and incentivize the deepening of the FX market (including the use of FX hedging instruments). To complement this more restrained approach to FX intervention, further institutional and technical reforms would be useful to improve the functioning of the FX market and strengthen market participants’ ability to manage currency risks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/">Costa Rica inflation moderates fall in September</a> appeared first on <a href="//wwv.nacion.com">WWV Nacion</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>//wwv.nacion.com/costa-rica-inflation-moderates-fall-in-september/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
